♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hey, guys, I didn't know you were
coming to the church raffle.
I will confess a mix-up to you.
I thought Donna said we were
going to the "church waffle."
And we're only here for the
fantasy weekend at Fenway Park.
Fenway Park?
Oh, yeah, the winner and
a friend get to hang out
and practice with
retired Red Sox players
and then play in a real game,
right on the field at Fenway.
Oh, my God, that's always
been a dream of mine!
Well, that and tuning a guitar
in front of a live audience.
This was in perfect tune
when they handed it to me.
Next up, our fantasy weekend
for two at Fenway Park.
Oh, man, this is it!
And the winner is...
Peter Griffin!
Holy crap, I won!
- Wow, good for you!
- Congratulations!
I like it when people
say your name out loud!
How exciting, Peter.
A weekend trip to Boston.
Yeah, and the best part is,
I don't even have to get on a plane.
I always have trouble at the airport.
Sir, you're not allowed
to be on the carousel.
Well, then maybe you shouldn't
have named it such a fun word.
Uh, excuse me, excuse me, I'm not yours.
He's stealing me! I'm being stolen!
Excuse me, I think you've got mine.
Oh, that's a good idea.
- Oh, hey, Quagmire.
- Hey, Peter.
So I was just baking a coffee cake,
and I figured I'd bring it over,
'cause you like coffee cake.
Wow, thanks.
Yeah, yeah, no problem.
- So, who are you taking to Fenway?
- What?
Well, I was just thinking,
you have that extra ticket,
- maybe you'd want to...
- Peter, before you answer him,
I've got that murdered jogger's
Discman you wanted last week.
Still bloody.
Hi, Peter. You know how
you like $40 cash?
Well, here's almost $40 cash.
Guys, look, I know you all want to go,
but I-I need a little more
time to figure this out.
I mean, it's a tough decision.
Like what to do with that
big watermelon I bought.
Griffin, I just wanted to tell you...
that's a great outfit.
Keep it up.
I knew it.
I have to start trusting myself more.
Man, I don't envy you.
Whichever one of them
you bring to Fenway,
the other two will be mad at you.
I don't want to bring any of them.
Those guys are all way
better than me at baseball.
They'd just show me up
and ruin it for me.
Why don't you bring Lois?
She doesn't care about baseball,
and that way nobody gets
their feelings hurt.
Brian, that's a great idea.
Thanks.
- Is it new-tennis-ball great?
- It's three-new-tennis-balls great.
I'm gonna get 'em all,
I'm gonna get 'em all!
Mom, you're really going to Boston?
I didn't even think you liked baseball.
Oh, I'm not going for baseball,
I-I'm going for shopping, the hotel spa,
and two days of being away
from you life-sucking turds.
Anyway, be good.
And while we're gone, Brian's in charge.
Where is Brian?
What's up, bitches?
Oh, come on, Mom, really?
I'm in high school,
and you're still putting
the dog in charge?
Believe me, Meg, you want me in charge.
Stewie can be a bit of a handful.
He's right, you know.
I'm a total Taurus,
stubborn as they come.
All right, fine, Meg.
While we're away, you can be in charge.
Come on, Lois, time to get to Fenway.
Wow, Dad, you look awesome.
But I thought you were gonna
dress like a baseball player.
I am, Chris.
I'm the type of player who arrives
at the stadium in a suit.
With a tie knot as big as an apple.
That's how you know I got mon-ay.
All right, we'll see you guys Sunday.
Okay, now you heard Mom
say I'm in charge,
so I just want to lay
a few ground rules.
Yeah.
I promise we're gonna have fun,
- but there will be a schedule just...
- Uh-huh.
- To keep everything running smoothly.
- Sure, got to have boundaries.
- And I may assign a chore or two...
- That's great, Meg.
- Because it's actually more fun...
- Sounds like you got it all worked out.
- When everyone pitches in.
- Hey, by the way...
Ah!
I'm gonna flush your
retainer down the toilet.
Look at this, Lois, the
Fenway Park locker room.
All right, Peter, I'm gonna go.
You want to hand me some cash
in front of the other men
so you feel powerful?
Instead, why don't you just
take my Minions Discover Card?
Hey, there, sluggers.
Welcome to Red Sox Fantasy Weekend.
Well, who's this?
We've never had a lady
come out for this before.
Oh, no, no, that's my wife,
she's just dropping me off.
Yeah, you're nice, but I'm not staying.
I don't know the first
thing about baseball.
Look, your spot's already paid for.
And besides, if you leave,
the teams will be lopsided.
So, as your coach, I insist
you stay and play with us.
Right, fellas?
Well, I don't know.
What do you think, Peter?
What do I think about sharing
fantasy baseball camp
with my wife?
Yeah, come on, let her play.
Wow, 1980s All-Star Wade Boggs!
Hey, would you mind standing
next to a star of today?
Sure.
Man, what happened to our game?
David Ortiz, will you
pick him up like a baby?
It's your weekend.
Now let me put this
baby bonnet on his head
and a cigar in his mouth.
So, what do you say?
Are you gonna let your wife play?
Absolutely.
Lois, stay here and play with us.
I can't say no to Baby Boggs.
Coochie-coochie-coo... Ah, he bit me.
Oh, my God, I can't believe I'm here.
Lois, see that wall there?
They call that "the Green Monster."
And over there's where I threw a
D-cell battery at Jos├й Canseco.
All right, let's play ball.
Wow, you must be excited, Peter.
Yep, guess I can cross this
one off my bucket list.
All that's left now is
living the pueblo lifestyle.
Peter, what the hell did
you do to the house?
I know, it seems pretty lame
until you realize I'm 58.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I
have to go lick the foot
of a fleshy, pale woman for Real Sex 34.
Rupert, what do you think of
this fan fiction I wrote?
"Diego pressed Dora against the wall,
her bosom heaving,
her hot Latina breath on his face.
For once, Diego was going
to do the exploring."
Whew, just reading it...
muy caliente.
Okay, Stewie, time for
you to get dressed.
Yeah, a closed door means
"come in," I guess.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Let's pick out a cute shirt for you.
Then I thought we can go to the park.
Or, how about this?
I press my butt against
the wall and dook on it?
Stewie!
Don't do that!
You're messing with my schedule,
so I'm giving you wall poo.
Stop that right now.
You just earned a time-out.
A what? Let go of me!
Don't you walk away!
Hey, don't bruise me, I'm
going dancing later.
You listen to me, you little monster,
I take abuse from everybody around here,
but I am not gonna take it from you.
Now sit here until I say you can get up.
And if you move one muscle before then,
I'll smack you in your weird head.
Hey, it's not weird.
Mom says it's distinctive.
Griffin, you're up.
It's always the fat one.
I heard that.
I said it right to you.
You know what?
Let's just get Lois up to bat.
Where's Lois?
I'm right here, Coach.
Guess you don't have a
lot of babes out here.
Except for Babe Ruth.
- Babe Ruth.
- Ha!
That's funny 'cause she's hot.
Ah, it's a little like tennis.
Uh, did you see that, Peter?
I'm doing it all!
Damn it. This is supposed
to be my weekend.
Stewie?
What the hell's going on?
Meg's awful!
She gave me a time-out and she
made me sit in this chair.
My God, she put eye shadow on you, too.
I might've gotten up from the chair.
Brian, Meg's lost her mind.
You've got to talk to her.
Stewie, Lois put Meg in charge,
and, honestly, once I knew that,
I ate a pot cookie.
So, um, yeah.
So good luck with all that.
Uh, you got any cool DVDs?
Brian, please, I need help.
Totally.
Hey, where's Chris?
I wonder if he'll play
Wii bowling with me.
All right, that's it, I'm
not just gonna sit here
and see what that psycho does next.
All right, think.
Ah!
I shall fashion a makeshift ladder
with my Diaper Genie entrails,
shimmy down to the yard,
and I'm free.
The trick, Chris, is
thinking of the wand
as an extension of your arm.
Wow, I can't believe I'm pretend bowling
with a dog on drugs!
Ah! Son of a bitch!
Oh, my God, a baby!
My name's Shelly.
I can't have any of my own.
Would you like to come home with me?
I love you so much.
Ah! Everywhere's a nightmare!
Wow, it's nice they put
on a banquet for you.
It looks like I'm the only woman here.
Yeah, they're ex-athletes,
which means they're all divorced.
In fact, their ex-wives are
having a banquet next door
with their money.
Oh, they're having fun.
They're doing a lot of pointing dancing.
Well, at least somebody's
having fun here tonight.
Oh, you're just nervous about
the big game tomorrow.
I-Is it 'cause of how pink
you turn when you run?
A couple guys mentioned
that today on the field.
What? Who said that?
I don't know, "N-Nomar" something.
You met Nomar?!
Hey, there you are.
We've been saving a spot
at the head table for you
with all the Hall-of-Famers.
Oh, thanks.
Finally something's going my way.
- Where should I...
- Not you. Lois.
What?
This is the one night of the year
they let me out of the scoreboard.
Oh, I don't know if I deserve
to sit at the head table.
No, no, we took a vote.
We all want to sit next to you.
You're the only one
here who doesn't have
a fistful of baseball
cards for us to sign.
I wasn't gonna have 'em sign 'em.
I was just gonna tell 'em their stats.
But this is Peter's weekend.
Aw, don't worry about Peter.
Now, come on, Lois,
we've got you sitting
right between Pedro Martinez
and Ted Williams' severed head.
There's a special place in hell
for whoever's responsible
for me ending up like this.
Hey, Meg, is anybody gonna
eat this grilled cheese?
No, don't eat that.
That's Stewie's lunch.
Oh, my God, Stewie!
I forgot, he's been in a
time-out for six hours.
Stewie? Oh, no, where is he?
He's gone... I'm gonna
be in so much trouble.
I tried to tell you,
watching Stewie wasn't easy.
Oh... Aw, man, this is terrible.
Stewie could be anywhere.
Sorry, I forgot my jacket.
Okay, everybody, we're gonna
do some double-play drills.
Oh, yeah, a little infield.
Let's flash some leather, huh, guys?
Who wants to play second?
I will.
Lois, why don't you take second?
How could he not see that?
I even held up my arm
with my other hand.
That is the most noticeable way
to raise your hand.
Okay, Griffin, you go out there
and be the base runner.
All right, Peter, show 'em what you got.
Okay, Lois, catch the ball,
and if your foot comes off the bag,
just tag Peter on any part of his body.
How could I miss, right?
It'll be like tagging a barn.
Sorry, Peter, that's baseball.
I'll show you baseball, you
sexually unsatisfied wife!
Oh.
Yeah! Now, that's a
big-league slide, huh, coach?
Damn it!
I think it's broken.
Griffin, what are you, an idiot?
Yeah, an idiot who's gonna show up
on SportsCenter tonight.
Coming up after the break,
we'll have highlights of the
playoff game between...
Streaking. Unrelated.
Yep, her leg is fractured.
We should get her to the hospital.
My only medical training
is to say "Walk it off."
- Can you walk it off?
- No!
Oh, well, that's not good.
Okay, I'm gonna go fake-use
the phone in the dugout.
Peter, what the hell got into you?
Nothing. I was just trying to
play hard, like Pete Rose.
Look, I can even do the
Pete Rose haircut.
I bet you a thousand bucks
I have a drinking problem.
Guys, we got to get that leg set.
I guess I should ride in the ambulance.
You think I'll be back
in time for the game?
What? You're not playing in the game.
It's supposed to be a fun day out here,
and you go nuts and
break your wife's leg.
It's not my fault, I'm all hopped up
on hard baseball card gum.
Mmm, it's like eating a MasterCard.
Let's get her out of here.
And you, you're done.
Clean out your locker!
Kicked out? I'm totally screwed.
Like those poor guys who had to come up
with a new ad campaign for Subway.
Hey, I'm Mike.
I like sandwiches and people my own age.
Subway... please don't
think of pedophilia.
You know what I'm
getting sick of saying?
"My husband did this to me,
but it's not what you think."
Please forgive me, Lois. I'm so stupid.
The reason I didn't bring my friends is
'cause I didn't want 'em
hogging the spotlight.
And then when I saw everyone
giving you all that attention,
I-I guess I kind of lost it.
You did a little.
But of course I forgive you.
I just don't understand
why you went so crazy.
Well, ever since I was little,
I was always the fat, uncoordinated kid
that nobody wanted on their team.
And I was excited that for one weekend,
if I could just step on that field
and get a hit at Fenway Park,
I could erase all that
and feel like a champ
for the first time in my life.
But I'm not a champ, I'm a fat loser.
No wonder nobody ever picked me.
I picked you, Peter.
And to me and our kids, you
will always be a winner.
Thanks, Lois.
And you know what? If that's true,
I don't need to play in some stupid
fantasy baseball game.
Well, guess what.
You're gonna play in that game,
and you're gonna get that hit.
And when you do, we're
all gonna be there
to cheer you on.
Really? Well, how's that gonna happen?
Peter, these guys have
been sexually harassing me
since the second I got here.
Either you play, or every
one of these Red Sox
are going to jail... Even Ted Williams.
Mmm, new meat.
I think we're gonna get along just fine.
This is the number-one fear
of only being a head.
Brian, do you always listen to
the Sirius XM preview station?
Yeah, I'm thinking about
pulling the trigger,
but they make you sign,
like, a two-year...
Guys, who cares about your dumb radio?!
We can't find Stewie anywhere.
Hello. Oh, hi, Mom.
Hi, honey. How you doing?
How's Stewie?
Oh, he's great. Not lost or anything.
How's fantasy camp going?
Uh, your father broke
my leg out of jealousy,
but that didn't ruin our honeymoon,
and it's not gonna ruin this.
So listen, I want all you guys
to drive up to Boston this afternoon
to see your father play in the big game.
Uh, wow, we'd love to...
Mom, but we promised Stewie
we'd perform a puppet
show for him later today.
Oh, you can perform it for
all of us up here in Boston.
The game's in two hours.
Drive safely.
Crap! Now we got to find Stewie
and write a puppet show.
We could repurpose my one-act farce.
Or we could write something fresh.
Look, just because it's
already been written
doesn't mean it's not fresh.
What did I just say? Shut up!
We're in trouble. I'm in trouble.
Hey, what's this, a dickweed convention?
Stewie!
Oh, thank God you're home!
Where the hell have you been?
As far away from her as possible.
I forgot her name, honestly.
- Who, Meg?
- Yes, yes, Meg. She's scary and mean,
and I don't ever want her
to be in charge of me.
Are you afraid of me, little guy?
Oh, Stewie, I'm really sorry
I left you in that time-out.
I love you very much, and
I'm so happy you're home.
You're my little brother.
Can you forgive me?
Well... all right.
Can I have your baby?
Don't let her in!
We're all proud of you, Peter.
N-Now, don't be nervous.
I ain't nervous, Lois...
I'm just sweating
'cause I was too embarrassed to
get nude in the locker room,
so I'm wearing all this
over long pajamas.
Ladies and gentlemen, now batting
for the Boston Red Sox, Peter Griffin!
Fair ball! Run, Peter! Run it out!
Peter's Brain.
Yeah, uh, this is the Muscle Department.
What the hell is he doing?
Uh, apparently, he's trying to sprint.
Sprint? He got winded
walking to the plate.
And he's been out in the
blazing sun for two days.
Has he had any water?
No. He told his wife there's
juices in the hot dogs.
Well, I'm sorry, I got no choice
but to call for a
complete muscle failure.
Look! Dad's planking,
from, like, eight years ago!
Is there a Neiman Marcus in Boston?
Peter! Get up! Get up and run!
- Run, Peter!
- Come on, Dad!
- We love you!
- Copley Place. How far is that?
I ran like a champion that
day, pushing through the pain
of two torn hamstrings
and a ruptured groin,
to leg out the hit at Fenway Park
I had always dreamed of.
But nobody noticed, 'cause the
account manager from B of A
who was playing third base
had a massive coronary
trying to field my crappy little nubber.
The hit was amazing, but
what made it even better
was that my family was there
to share the moment with me.
And on the car ride home,
they put on a puppet show
that made me laugh so hard
I crashed into a tollbooth
on the Mass Pike, totaling the car
and breaking Lois's other leg.
The casts kind of smell,
so I won't let her sleep in
the bedroom till they're off.
But that's baseball.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru